Kheel Center Additional Office Files /4049
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Kheel Center Additional Office Files
1978-1981
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations (NYSSILR)
Martin P. Catherwood Library
Labor-Management Documentation Center
Kheel Center
/4049
2 cubic feet
2 linear ft.
Records (documents).
3084997
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, January 13, 2016
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, September 23, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /4012: Kheel Center Files and Circulation Reserve List /4051: Kheel Center Additional Office Files /4072: Kheel Center Additional Files /4074: Kheel Center Additional Office Files, User Applications /4088: Kheel Center Office Files /4105: Kheel Center Additional Researcher Correspondence /4141: Kheel Center Additional Administrative Files
Martin P. Catherwood Library.; Martin P. Catherwood Library. Labor-Management Documentation Center.; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations.; Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives.
3084997
- SP - African Labor Leader Oral History Project, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- SP - Agricultural Labor Guide, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- SP - CETA Grant, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- SP- Conrail History Project, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Conservation Discussion Sheets, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Conservation Committee - Instructions for Minor Repairs to Library Volumes (Box 1, Folder 6)
- SP - Fact-Finding Sample Project, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- SP - Paul - Conservation, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Fumigant Sterilizer - Fumigants - SP, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- SP - Guides - other Repositories, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- SP - Guide to the Records, 1954-1956 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- SP - Guide to the Records, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- SP - Guide to the Records, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- SP - Honary Archivist Project (Box 1, Folder 14)
- SP - Ives Biography Project, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- SP - LMDC Brochure, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- SP - Library Resources and Services Committee (C.U.L.), 1976 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- SP - Management and Personnel Theory Documentation Project, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- SP NYS Archives Evaluation Project, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- SP - NYS Conservation/Preservation Project, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- SP - NYS Historian's Mailing 1/76, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- SP - Nucmc Data Sheets (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Personnel - Manuscript Cataloger (Katherine Armendt), 1979 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Personnel - Manuscript Cataloger (Rosemary H. Burke), 1979 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Personnel - Manuscript Cataloger (Bradley Collier), 1979 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Personnel - Manuscript Cataloger (Martha Crowe), 1979 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Personnel - Manuscript Cataloger (Maureen Fuller), 1953 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Personnel - Manuscript Cataloger (Jennifer C. Cage), 1979 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Personnel - Manuscript Cataloger (Michael Nombrea), 1976 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Personnel - Manuscript Cataloger (Thomas M. Parrish), 1979 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Personnel - Manuscript Cataloger (Doreen Roberts), 1979 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Senior Assistant Archivists Files Application Glanks Description (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Personnel - Sr. Assistant Archivist - General File, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Personnel - Senior Assistant Archivist (Unacceptable Candidates), 1958 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Personnel - Manuscript Cataloger (Robert E. Bailey), 1979 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Personnel - Senior Asst. Archivist (Elizabeth Jean Currie), 1979 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Personnel - Assistant Archivist (Frederick J. Heuser, Jr.), 1980 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Personnel - Senior Assistant Archivist (Lawrence Hibpshman), 1980 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Personnel - Senior Assistant Archivist (Terry S. Latour) (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Personnel - Seniority Archivist (James McEnery), 1979 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Personnel - Senior Assistant Archivist (Sandy Menegaux), 1979 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Personnel - Senior Assistant Archivist (Nancy S. Osborne), 1979 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Personnel - Senior Assistant Archivist (Inga Wild), 1979 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Personnel - Senior Asst. Archivist (Donna Webber), 1973-1980 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- SP - Processing Manual (2nd Edition), 1974 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- SP - Processing Manual, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- SP - Publication Form (Box 2, Folder 25)
- SP - Repository Guide Copy, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- SP - Restoration of Mss., 1973 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- SP - Syracuse Univ. Field Working Placement, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- SP - UTU Brochures, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- SP - UTU Exhibits, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- SP - UTU Publicity 1969-70, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- SP -UTU Publicity 1971-73, 1971-1973 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- SP - Oral History, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- SP - Oral History - Catherwood, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- SP - Oral History - Ching, Cyrus, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- SP - Oral History - Counts, Davidson Schappes and Hook, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 36)
- SP. Photograph Project (School) (Box 2, Folder 37)
- SP Photograph Project (School) (Box 2, Folder 38)
- SP - Photograph Workshop, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 39)